Big Sis, Sir Tooka...
Lis.
Remember what Sir Tooka said?
He has the best chance
of survival in this situation.
Sir Tooka would never lie without reason.
I'm sure that he'll come back with Eve.
My throat... I can't speak...
This thing can still move,
even after eating my Stage Two?
Her precision is growing with every thrust.
She's the type to mature
in real combat, is she?!
Found it.
Oh no!
Itsuki.
I've been waiting for you, Sis.
I see Kashima-san's safe.
Well, it was a pretty close call.
Sis...
Can I ask why you stopped me
from delivering the final blow?
That isn't a monster.
Huh?
Her disposition isn't like those
we've fought thus far.
A lioness, huh?
A leopard.
Huh?
So, like, does it make any difference?
What sets her apart
from a monster is her intelligence.
The will in her eyes
and the way she carries herself
actually strike me as closer to human.
Meaning... what, exactly?
We can most likely communicate
in earnest with her.
But it doesn't seem like she can talk.
It seems you disabled
her voice with your attack.
Wait, I did? Did I screw up?
Shit, I did...
I messed up big-time.
First, allow me to apologize
for my younger sister.
She tends to jump the gun,
and she prioritized my orders such
that she rushed in recklessly.
I-I-I'm sorry.
I have a habit of leaping to action
when my sister's not around.
That said, my instructions were lacking.
- That said, my instructions were lacking.
- She seems reasonable,
but she's got her guard up.
- Now, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
- She seems reasonable,
but she's got her guard up.
Now, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
I know you still can't talk,
so could I ask you to answer with gestures?
- I know you still can't talk,
- This feeling...
so could I ask you to answer with gestures?
- It's different...
Do you bear any hostility for the three of us?
Then do you have any issue
with us all parting ways?
But they remind me of Tooka.
Who is this woman?
Hijiri Takao. That's my name.
We're humans from another world.
Why identify yourself...?
She spoke!
- Thank goodness!
- A show of courtesy...
- If she never spoke again,
I'd be racked with guilt forever!
- Eve Speed.
Quick to let your reactions
show on your face, are you?
I heard the rumors of a leopardman
bloodsport warrior who went missing.
You... aren't alone, are you?
Perhaps you're searching for someone
you've been separated from.
Exactly.
I'm looking for my liege.
If you're so intent on finding them,
that suggests you anticipate that
they weathered the monster stampede, yes?
Meaning your liege possesses the ability to
survive an encounter with human-faced beasts.
Your insight is stunning.
However, my liege cannot be
gauged by such a simple measure.
Now I'm even more intrigued.
Paralyze!
Berserk! Berserk! Berserk!
Piggymaru!
Sleep!
Poison!
TOOKA MIMORI
- I still have MP in reserve.
But Piggymaru's...
You did a great job.
I bet you're well past your limit, too.
If you really feel yourself hitting it,
let me know. Don't hide it.
I'll handle the rest from there.
Once we part ways,
I'll leave Seras and the others to you.
Must've gotten banged up in that fall..
Still, I've made it this far.
Status: Open.
TOOKA MIMORI
E-CLASS HERO
- I've even reached Level 2,000.
TOOKA MIMORI
E-CLASS HERO
- But my energy and wounds don't recover
TOOKA MIMORI
E-CLASS HERO
- no matter how high my values climb.
I'm starting to feel weak, too.
Also...
There's one left.
Most likely a human-faced beast.
You've been watching all this time, right?
I can't inflict anything on it
without line of sight.
That's the most crucial condition
to activating my status ailment skill.
And this last human-faced beast
has picked up on that.
This is the final stage of our battle.
RULER AND SWORD
Slei!
Piggymaru...
Sorry, but could I ask you
to do one last job for me?
Paralyze!
Your real target is above you!
Berserk!
Yeah, that's right.
I used my mask as a decoy
and made you think,
"This is a trap. He's going to flank me."
Then, while you were distracted by Piggymaru,
I leapt into the air
so I could get a full view of you.
You were preventing me from
using my skill by hiding yourself,
except that also meant...
you couldn't see me either.
Status: Open.
TOOKA MIMORI
- I'm surprised I've hit critical.
You have leveled up.
Your Paralyze Skill has leveled up.
An advanced skill has been unlocked.
An advanced skill?
Sorry for pushing you guys so hard.
Now, shall we head back
to Seras and the others?
My legs are in bad shape.
I have plenty of MP.
It'll all come down to my stamina.
Par—
Ah...
I had a feeling this might happen.
I've found you, my liege.
I get Slei and Piggymaru, but me too?
My strength is one of my best assets.
While I was searching for you,
I encountered heroes from another world.
Hijiri Takao, Itsuki, and
another girl called Kashima.
The Takao sisters and Kashima, huh?
And what of my name?
I did not give it.
I didn't know what their
relationship with you was like.
Yeah, good call.
It's best if Mimori Touka stays dead to them.
It's easy to imagine the 2-C heroes becoming
an obstacle to my revenge on the goddess.
Your mind is still turning even when
you're gravely injured, isn't it?
I'd honestly love to find somewhere
we can take a break, though.
Slei?
And...
Sir Tooka!
Big Sis! Sir Tooka!
Little Slei and Piggymaru!
Big Sis!
I came back alive, just as I promised.
Ahem.
Sir Tooka,
I'm glad to see you safe.
Seras, could you check on Slei for me?
Well then, I'll go stand watch.
Sorry.
I know you're probably tired too.
My fatigue is nothing compared to yours.
I'm done.
You're able to tend wounds,
and you can wield a sword.
I couldn't ask for more.
I also know how to sew.
I'd appreciate it.
Leave it to me.
You can't sleep?
Guess I'm still too on edge for that.
But even so, just lying down
is an improvement.
Well, I'm not sure if this well help
calm your nerves or not, but...
Get some sleep.
Um, to be honest, I'm tense too,
so I don't feel like I could rest.
I get it. She's just pretending right now.
Then I'll take you up on that.
I haven't really slept in someone's lap
since my aunt let me do it ages ago.
Seras?
Please don't carry everything
all by yourself.
Did I look that worn down?
Even when all the creatures in this
Land of Monsters beset us at once,
you put on a brave face and acted
as if it were nothing to you.
Eve and Lis were reassured to see it, but...
I guess you could sense the lies mixed in.
Yes.
Sometimes I get scared.
Scared that one day you'll charge
yourself with a task too heavy
and you'll suddenly fall apart.
That worries me.
Seras.
If you insist on worrying about me,
then support me as best you
can so that doesn't happen.
Yes.
Trust that I will, Sir Tooka.
- I'll kill you, brat!
- I've been regaining the Touka I was back then.
- Just try and break me if you can!
- Had I stayed the "normal"
person I became over time,
I'm sure this world would've
broken me long ago.
So for now...
this is fine.
However, please come to me without reservation
whenever it becomes hard for you.
If there's anything I can do to help,
I'll happily oblige however I can.
You're such an overprotective vice captain.
I would rather you say I'm devoted.
Maybe this is what it's like
to have an older sister.
Speaking of, Sir Tooka, how old are you?
Hmm? I'm seventeen.
What? You're younger than me?
Well, of course I am.
High elves are longer-lived
than humans, right?
Nineteen.
Is that your age?
I was convinced you must've
lived for a century or so.
Wait, hold on.
How old did you think I was?
I thought you were in your
early or mid-twenties.
Um, you're just so calm about everything.
I see.
There's so much I still don't
know about you, isn't there?
I could say the same.
So, do you plan on treating me
like a younger brother now?
No, you are the ruler of the
Lord of the Flies' War Band.
Even if you're younger than me,
I shall not regard the ruler
I swore loyalty to any differently.
I'm not really fit to be a ruler, you know?
No, Sir Tooka.
You are my dear, one and only
ruler right now.
I see...
Sir Tooka?
Have you fallen asleep already?
Truly, you were utterly worn out, weren't you?
Sir Tooka...
So this is what Sir Tooka looks
like when he's acting his age...
I never thought I would feel
this way for someone.
So this is...
Sir Tooka?
Sir Tooka...
This is...
What... was I about to...
Hmm?
Seras.
You can't sleep?
I'm terribly sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
F-Forgive me.
Shall I use my skill to put you to sleep?
Please.
Sleep.
I see...
At some point, I started letting myself
be that vulnerable around you, huh?
Once again, thank you very much, Takao-san.
Whoa, you're super formal, Kashima.
You can call me Itsuki.
My sister and I are both Takaos, you know?
By the way, I wanted to ask you something.
S-Sure. What is it?
Why are you in Asagi's group?
Huh?
You're way more like the class prez,
no matter how you cut it.
Well, it's because...
Man, I knew you couldn't do it.
Good thing I'm here
for our timid little pigeon.
Let me help you with that.
Good job, little pigeon!
You've passed the test,
and that settles things!
Humanity has always survived
by joining hands, meow.
But if we don't start helping
each other after joining up,
then we end up crushing each other, woof.
So we all need to look
after one another, cluck.
Kobato-san, are you listening to me?
So I'm going to stick with Asagi-san's group.
Asagi's kinda got a dangerous
vibe though, you know?
Yes, I know.
And someday, that might
be what saves Sogou-san.
Huh?
Um, Sir Tooka?
What is it?
There's something I'd like
to confess to you one day.
"One day," huh?
Yes.
Right now I lack the courage to do so.
So please give me some time.
All right.
I know it's unfair to make this so one-sided.
But if I confess, then I
might lose Sir Tooka's trust.
However, I have to tell him eventually,
even if he curses me for it
and even if it destroys
our current relationship.
If Seras hasn't realized that I already know,
then things are fine as they are for now.
I know Seras will eventually come clean.
I'll tell him I love him,
which terrifies me more
than crossing swords with any foe.
So, Sir Tooka,
please give me time to muster my courage.
Until then...
I will be my ruler's sword.
I will play the role of Seras's liege.
WITCH'S TERRITORY
- This is a magic seal.
This is a magic seal.
Is it the kind that triggers
a trap under certain conditions?
A portion of the formula is damaged,
so it probably won't activate.
It looks rather old as well.
It's old?
I really hope we're not looking at a situation
where the witch turns out to be dead already.
What is that?
Similar seals?
Looks like this one's live.
Paralyze!
Well, it's probably a golem to welcome
invaders or something like that.
Should we shatter it to be safe?
No, I don't want to destroy stuff recklessly
and make the witch think
we're hostile toward her.
I can't believe I'm not
sensing a single monster.
I guess we're definitely in the
witch's territory now.
Are those golems too?
Looks like I don't need my skill.
They're just quietly working away.
Tooka.
I just hope it opens with
magic like we theorized.
Now I see.
The witch didn't bother to hide this thing
because it consumes an
extraordinary amount of magic.
However, my magic capacity
is one thing I'm confident in.
Eve.
Kashima-san!
- Sogou—
- Little pigeon!
I was so worried about you!
Asagi-san, I'm sorry I worried you.
So, why are you with the Takaos?
We ran into each other,
and they helped me out.
Huh. Guess the Takaos are pretty nice.
Kashima-san.
I'm glad...
I'm so glad you're safe.
Sogou-san...
It's okay. Takao-san and her sister saved me.
The Four Saints are still out looking for you,
so I'll go tell them we've found you.
O-Okay.
Boy, am I glad all our allies
made it out unharmed.
It's okay that I'm still a timid,
foolish pigeon for now.
But I have to get stronger.
Looks like we made the right call
to go search for Kashima-san.
Those soldiers we found in the forest...
This is still only speculation,
but I think their goal was
to assassinate the students of 2-C.
And I'm not talking about
just one or two of us.
What do you mean?
If Kashima-san had died,
it would have made a
terrible impact on Sogou-san.
I see.
If her heart were to break now,
it's easy to imagine what would follow.
That would be very boring.
There's a sky underground?
Incredible!
Must be the power of magic.
That, or we entered another space
after passing through the door.
There's even a breeze.
Tooka.
Yeah.
I'd wager that's...
who we've been seeking.
The Witch of Taboos.
If the rumors are correct,
she's the only one capable of deciphering
the scroll of forbidden magic.
She'll be our only lead on how
to exact revenge upon the goddess.
Send word to the Four Saints.
The Great Demon Empire's
forces are on the move,
- and they should recall the heroes at once.
- Ma'am!
Now, I wonder how wounded and how much
stronger the heroes will be when they return...
I can't wait to find out.
- Now then, I wonder if you can
use the ancient language.
- It certainly wasn't an easy road to get here.
- It was a cruel path that wore on our nerves.
- You mean this one?
Nevertheless, we made it.
Now this is where things start.
Let me first introduce myself.
My name is Erica Anaorovael.
ERICA ANAOROVAEL
DARK ELF, WITCH OF TABOOS
- My name is Erica Anaorovael.
I am indeed the one you
call the Witch of Taboos.
Just you wait, Vicius...
I'll annihilate everything of yours!